My name is Lara.
I'm the Little Mermaid
resurrected after 200 years.
But I've lost everything.
The ocean, my family, and
everything that binds them.
The light...
To bring them back,
I must do whatever
I can to find true love.
I was unable to find
true love back then,
but this time I know I will.
And that is why...
I've decided to look
for my prince again,
right here in Shiga!
[sighs]
See you later.
[♪ rousing orchestral
music begins]
My name is Mari.
I'm a freshman at
Zeze Minami High School.
I run every morning at 5 a.m.
My favorite things are my
pet Gon-chan and boxing.
[grunts]
I started boxing
with my brother.
And I've been doing it
for 10 years.
My goal is to be stronger
than anyone else.
I won't let anyone get in
my way, no matter what.
[grunting continues]
[♪ upbeat music]
[NAGAHAMA] Well, well, well,
look who's full of energy.
[MARI] She is Nagahama.
[NAGAHAMA] Undefeated
in official matches.
I'm the champ in this town.
Nice try, Otsu.
I really don't like you.
[LARA] Mari!
[panting]
What an idiot.
[♪ opening music begins]
[♪ opening music ends]
Mmm! So good!
This thing you call
rice is delicious!
Well, don't worry, it's
not going anywhere.
Mari's friend really does
enjoy eating rice.
Well, it certainly takes
some guts to stick with
Shiga's very own top
boxer the way you have.
-Stick with?
-Here, have some of this.
What is it?
Mmm! Whatever, it is delicious!
What am I going to do?
I've brought a mermaid
home with me, and she's weird.
I'm heading out for the day.
I'll be back later this evening.
[door opens and closes]
[LARA] Hey, Mari!
Where are you going?
-School?
-Say, Mari, what is... school?
It's a place where
people gather.
So how many people?
[LARA] Ten? Twenty?
I'd say there's around 600.
[gasps]
[LARA] So then is school the
name of a kingdom?
[MARI] You idiot.
[grunts]
[punching bag thudding]
[grunting]
More!
Harder!
Faster!
Stronger!
[♪ dramatic music]
Believe me, I know exactly what
children these days are like.
But, how many times has
this happened now?
Offering cake to apologize
simply won't cut it.
[MARI] Hm.
[sighs]
You've been fighting with
your school friends a lot,
so the house is
full of Baumkuchen.
If you keep picking fights,
Mom's going to get really fat.
It's fine because I really
like Baumkuchen.
Well, I really prefer kind kids
who don't fight just to
get some Baumkuchen.
It's not fair.
I did nothing wrong.
[sighs]
Hey, Mari.
What do you say
we have a fight?
A fight?
Whoever looks away first loses.
If you lose, you have to do
whatever I say.
Right, let's go.
Hmm.
Ah!
All right, looks like
I win the game.
[MARI] You cheated!
Let's play again!
Oh, no way. I say Mari
can't fight anymore, okay?
That's not fair though!
You cheated!
[Mari's mom giggles] Whoever
looks away first loses!
-Hey, Otsu!
-Ah?
Gonna stand there all day?
Oh, my bad. I didn't know
you were waiting.
Please try to follow
the gym rules.
-Yeah.
-What's with... that look?
-Huh?
-Looks like you wanna say
something, but you're
trying not to.
[MARI] No. What are
you getting at?
Can't you both go a day without
getting into an argument?
We're not arguing!
Otsu is doing the same workout
as the 2nd and 3rd years!
You can win the
nationals by doing
the same training as a rookie.
But she's just doing
middle school stuff!
[COACH] Nagahama, is it
really a captain's job
to nitpick the underclassmen?
-No, Coach.
-Then it's fine.
And Otsu, you're not innocent.
You two need to pay attention
and behave yourselves.
Right.
[LADY WITCH] The true love that
you once longed for so much
was never meant to be
because the prince rejected you.
You need to get over that,
overcome the pain and
fear that you felt back then.
In that case...
You must make it your
priority to find a new prince.
-A new prince?
-Exactly.
You need to find a new love with
a human somewhere.
Only then... are you able
to save your entire family.
[magical chimes]
-I know, but I'm scared.
-Of what?
[LARA] Venturing into the
outside world... without Mari.
My, how pathetic! Don't you
want to save your family?
You don't have time to be
worrying about things like this.
But if you're worried,
well, then...
just get Mari to help you.
Yes, she can be a difficult
girl, but if you trick her
well enough, then you
can get her to do anything.
Hmm?
Lara?
That's it! There's no way
I can carry on like this.
I need to do what I can to
understand this new world.
I need to connect more
and not be afraid!
I have to give it my all
and learn everything
about humans.
[water running]
Wow, that's... water!
Hey, Otsu,
you're just a junior, right?
I was fresh from being so cocky.
What are they
arguing about now?
They're discussing whether
to tape the gloves or not.
-Hmm.
-Uh, hey, Coach.
Can't you do something?
The tournament
is coming up soon.
-Otsu, Nagahama!
-Hmm?
You're both in the same
weight class, right?
Uh-huh.
The thing is, we're only sending
one of you to the match.
[both gasp]
We'll have a sparring
session tomorrow.
Whoever wins will be the one to
go to the match.
-Don't run away.
-I wouldn't dream of it.
Ah...
[Coach sighs] I'm looking
forward to tomorrow.
-I'm home.
-What a mess!
Wipe down every single
spot you walked on.
Okay.
[Mari sighs]
[Ema grumbles]
Gon-chan, what is her problem?
-I don't understand her.
-Oh, cut her some slack.
She's a mermaid.
And?
-[LARA] Mari!
-[MARI] Huh?
It looks like I need
something called money.
I've got no idea what
he's talking about.
What's going on out there?
Nothing!
[LARA] Haru is really amazing.
I just ask for things and look!
You've gotta be kidding me.
What did you do?
I just asked for some cake.
You like cake too, right?
That's what Lady Witch
told me anyway.
I actually first had
a spot of cake
a very long time ago and... oh!
This one has a weird shape.
[thud]
[Mari groans]
Clear your head.
Don't think about anything.
Don't look away.
Not for a second.
[crowd cheering on TV]
[YOSHIYA] Oh yeah!
[YOSHIYA] That's so cool.
-[Mari gasps]
- Yeah.
[MARI] Hey Mom,
let's have a fight.
Huh?
If you look away, you must
do whatever I say.
Oh, no way!
[Mari sighs]
[Mari grunts]
What's the matter?
I lost.
Well, that doesn't matter.
I want to go and try boxing.
Huh?
I want to try boxing.
Sure, you've been watching it
quite a lot lately, but...
that's pretty sudden.
-You sure?
-Mm-hmm.
Why didn't you tell
me you wanted this?
Because Mom says she likes
kids who don't get into fights.
Mari, the thing that I really
hate the most is
kids who look away
when it really matters.
It's perfectly fine to do
what you like, Mari.
But if you look away for one
second, you lose.
I'm sorry, uh, did I
distract you there?
[Lara shouts]
How about that kid?
You really need
to let me get in
touch with her parents.
I can't just let her stay here
without knowing the reason why.
Yeah.
If you find it hard to talk
about, I will tell them.
It's okay.
Is that so?
Hey, Mari, are you okay?
Huh?
I've noticed you've been
a bit on edge lately.
You worry too much, Grandma.
It's just... there's a big
match coming up.
[LARA] Mari!
[Lara panting] Mari!
Wait! Mari!
[Lara panting]
Finally, I caught up with you.
Gee, you're fast.
Hey, why are you following me?
Oh, that's not it.
I thought you might have
forgotten something.
This, I mean.
You always carry it, right?
What are you doing?
I don't bring it
every time I go for a run.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
-Hey.
-Huh?
What are you planning to do now?
I don't know what
Gon-chan told you, but
I can't let you stay in
my room much longer.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Right.
I'm sorry, but please
stop following me.
[magical chimes]
[shower running]
Whoa! What are you doing?
Being like this makes
me feel calm.
I'm sorry.
Hey, wait!
Um, did... Ah!
Dry yourself first!
[LADY WITCH] You made
Mari angry?
And you're going
to be kicked out?
This isn't going well.
If you carry on like this,
the chance of finding true love
will be nothing
but a pipe dream.
However, I suppose if you want
to borrow my power again...
Hey, Lady Witch?
How did you meet Mari
in the first place?
Hmm? Hmph. Just by chance.
She simply found me
and brought me here.
I guess my appearance must have
seemed slightly unusual to her.
What about this place?
Do you like living here?
[LADY WITCH] Oh no!
I can't wait for the day
that I can get out
of this cramped place.
But I did have Mari build
this aquarium for me, so...
it's not exactly the worst
place for a fish to live.
That's it!
I've decided.
I'm going to leave.
Huh?
I'm nothing like Lady Witch.
I could never take
advantage of anyone.
Hey, what are you doing?
I can't keep relying
on others all the time.
I won't cause any more
trouble for anyone, and
especially not for Mari.
Hey! Lara!
Huh?
All right, you two... ready?
Yeah.
[bell rings]
[grunting] [thudding]
[♪ intense music]
[Nagahama grunts]
[everyone gasps]
I got this.
-Hey!
-What are you?!
What's with the luggage?
-Where are you going?
-Hey!
Do you know where the
School Kingdom is?
-Right there!
-She's open!
Move!
[everyone shouting]
[grunts]
That's so cool, Mari!
Do you think so?
I think it's really
cool and fun!
[grunts]
Here...These will make
you much stronger.
[MARI] I won't lose to anybody!
You won again!
I have to keep my eyes on
the person in front of me.
Give it your all.
Show them what you've got.
I'll give it my all.
I'll always be my best self.
Always!
Nagahama!
Everyone is so loud.
You're making it
hard to concentrate!
[bell rings]
[everyone cheering]
What are you looking?!
[grunting] [thudding]
My rhythm's off?!
-All right!
- Shut up!
Nagahama!
[MARI] Shut up!
Everyone shut up!
-Shut up!
-Mari!
[gasps]
I don't understand
what's happening here!
Stop this at once!
Stop killing each other!
I won't let you hurt Mari, so
leave her alone, okay?
You idiot!
You can't step in the ring!
-Why, Mari?
-What are you doing here?
Oh, um, one moment.
Yoshiya bought this for me
earlier, but... Here.
I've decided I'm
going to move out,
so I wanted to thank you for
everything you've done for me.
Thank you.
But wait...
What's going on here?
Does everybody here
really hate you?
[laughing]
[MARI] Listen... I know I'm not
very good at being considerate,
so I end up causing
trouble for everyone.
But when boxing...
I want to face it head-on,
with dignity and pride.
But just now, I dropped
my concentration
and acted pathetically.
So, I'm sorry that
I looked away.
Please give me one more round!
Oh man, you're such
an unlikable brat.
Let's keep going.
[MARI] Lara... yesterday
I was a bit on edge.
I'm sorry,
but from now on, just keep
your eyes on me.
[bell rings]
[cheering]
I gotta say,
they're two of a kind.
[cheering]
[grunting] [thudding]
[bell rings]
Just be more
careful from now on.
I really don't get it.
So we both passed?
I mean, I definitely beat her.
[Mari sighs]
About that...
what were you trying to do?
I don't want to hear critiques.
-But what was that?
-Boxing.
-Boxing?
-A one-on-one sport.
[LARA] Um...
It's pretty cool, right?
You think?
I don't really get it.
-So, are you really leaving?
-Yeah.
-Do you have somewhere to go?
-Not really.
So what are you going to do?
I'll figure something out.
You'll just figure it out?
You are a mermaid who can't
live in the sea or on the land.
That's what Gon-chan said.
So tell me, what does that mean?
[LARA] Well, to be honest,
I'm still scared.
I'm scared that humans will
think I'm hideous again.
But...
I have made up my mind.
I'm going to make a
life for myself.
Uh...
I see.
Huh?
We'll figure something out.
Not sure if it'll
work out though.
So then does that mean I can go
back to your house?
Yeah.
But why?
Hum, you have a point.
I wonder why.
Probably because
you're an idiot.
An idiot?
That's right.
Funny idiots are cute.
[♪ magical music swells]
[♪ orchestral music]
[♪ music continues]
[singing]
Lady Lisa, what's that?
That girl's heart...
will become the light
that saves us all.
[♪ orchestral music continues]
[LISA] Lara, you must
find it soon.
For us...
please find true love.
[♪ closing music begins]
[♪ closing music ends]
Oh! Her father is...
that's right.
We can't get in touch
with anyone.
So then the rest
of the family are...
[sobs]
Oh, I see.
Of course, if there's anything
I can do to help at all.
Thank you for your help
in this difficult time.
Huh. Well, that's that done.
-Thank you very much, Gon-chan.
-That's gonna cost you.
I have absolutely no idea
what you're talking about,
but does that mean
I can still stay here?
Yes, unless you slip up,
that is.
[gasps]
Mari, you must try this!
-Oh...
-And this too!
You didn't buy this with
your own money, did you?
[LARA] Wow,
this is really delicious!
-What's it called?
- You idiot.
It melts in your mouth
like magic!
Look at this one!
This is the first
time I've had this.
Never seen or tasted
anything like it!